Welcome to AP US History Unit 7. This is
an enormous unit where we'll cover
imperialism, both world wars, the 20s,
the depression, the new deal. God, this
unit took forever to make. This unit
will be worth 10 to 17% on your AP exam.
And for those who are new here, this
video will simply be a clip together
video of all my e push unit 7 topic
review videos without the AP style
questions at the end of each topic. If
you'd like to try AP style questions at
the end of each topic, please feel free
to check out my unit 7 playlist. It will
be linked in the description. Also,
please consider helping me grow my
lovely Instagram. But anyway, let's get
into unit 7. To start off this unit,
before progressivism in US history,
there will be a very brief era of
imperialism. Imperialism here will
simply mean that the US will go out and
try to take other land and as a result
become a world global power. We already
talked about little examples like
Hawaii, and we'll get to the big example
next topic. For now, we need to talk
about debates over imperialism because
you have the side of people who
supported imperialism and the side who
didn't. This will be all we cover this
topic. So, let's try to go through this
debate as fast as we can. Imperialists
or those who support imperialism will
have mostly four arguments. One,
economics because imperializing will
lead to new markets and resources. Two,
power politics because Europe was
colonizing and the US didn't want to
fall behind. Three, racism/ a quote
civilizing mission because of the belief
that white Anglo-Saxon Protestants or
Wasps should quote uplift others. And
finally, four, the frontier was closed.
This idea was caused by the 1890 census
signaling westward expansion was
basically over. Examples of people in
this group are Alfred Theer Mahan and
Josiah Strong. Moving on to the
anti-imperialists. They will have three
arguments. One, self-determination,
meaning the idea of being an empire
contradicts US Republican ideals and the
literal Declaration of Independence. Two
is racism because people on this side
didn't really want non-white people
added to the US. And finally, three,
isolationism. They argued Americans
should keep their focus at home and
avoid overseas entanglements. A group to
reference here might be the
Anti-Imperialist League. And a few
people to note might be Andrew Carnegie
and Mark Twain. But for America's brief
little moment of imperialism at the end
of the 19th century, its biggest
campaign will easily be the
SpanishAmerican War. This war isn't like
many wars I'm sure you know.
Essentially, it started because Cuba
didn't want to be controlled by Spain
anymore, and the US was willing to
support Cuba in that regard. Propaganda
was also a big part with the growth of
yellow journalism. And the other part to
this is the sinking of the US ship, the
USS Main. Now, it's not actually truly
known what really caused the explosion
that sank this ship, but it didn't
really matter because US propaganda at
the time blamed it on Spain. As for the
war, it was actually quite quick. The US
will fight Spain and the war will be
fought in Cuba and the Philippines. And
the US Navy will crush Spain quickly.
The decisive battle of this war will be
the Battle of Manila Bay. And a big
propaganda group that will get traction
here is the Rough Riders, which was led
by Theodore or better known as Teddy
Roosevelt. This war will end with a
treaty that we will happily add to our
list of the many Treaty of Parises. This
treaty will cause Spain to give up
Puerto Rico, Guam, and the Philippines.
Puerto Rico will quietly become a US
territory. Guam will quietly become a US
naval base, and the Philippines will
become a colony of the US for $20
million, but they will not go quietly at
all. This will trigger a
PhilippineAmerican war where Filipinos
led by Ailio Aguinonaldo will want
independence, and the US will suppress
this nationalist movement severely. As
for Cuba, it will technically be
independent, but basically the US will
have a shitload of soldiers occupy the
country and impose a controlling plat
amendment. So, I'll leave the debating
up to you whether or not that's truly
independent. The other outcome of this
war is that the US will finally be
involved with Asia and open up a lot of
trade with different Asian countries
like China. Welcome to the progressive
era. Yes, it's truly time to talk about
the era following the guilded age. Let's
quickly define the progressive movement
in one sentence. progressives responded
to political corruption, social
injustice, and economic inequality
created and heightened by industrial
capitalism and urbanization. And I don't
want you to sit there and think this
progressive movement was one big unified
group, because it really wasn't. Rather,
it was a bunch of little movements that
had a lot of things in common, which is
why we roped them together into one big
progressive movement. Reformers were
often middle to upper class, and many
were women working, especially in cities
and among immigrant populations. The
biggest thing you'll see in this
movement is something called muckreers.
This means a journalist/ritider whom
investigates wrongdoing. Let's go
through some key figures in this regard.
Upton Sinclair was a muckraaker who
wrote the famous the jungle. This book
exposed disgusting meat packing and
pushed for food regulations. Ida Tarbell
is a muckraaker who investigated
Standard Oil and exposed their probably
illegal monopoly tactics. And finally,
Jacob Reese is a muckreaker who made the
book How the Other Half Lives, where the
book is packed full of photos and
reports exposing the horrid tenement
housing conditions. Moving on, let's go
over a different section of the
progressive movement, the political
side. Here we'll look at two people,
Theodore Roosevelt and Woodro Wilson.
Roosevelt argued for a quote square deal
where he pleaded to reign in
corporations, protect consumers, and
conserve natural resources. Wilson
argued for a quote new freedom by
restoring economic opportunity by
breaking up monopolies, lowering
tariffs, and reforming the banking
system. Notice how both of these ideals
are trying to regulate and reform most
of what the guilded age stood for. That
being said, there would also be a
movement of women's rights. We already
talked about the roots of this back in
unit 4 with the Senica Falls Convention,
though later I did forget to mention
Susan B. Anthony, so apologies about
that. But now you have activists like
Carrie Chapman Cat and Alice Paul along
with a lot of women rallying behind the
movement. This women's movement will
continue to grow and will eventually
contribute a lot to two amendments later
on. Now let's move over to
African-American rights. Many
progressives were split or simply
ignored segregation as a whole. As for
people advocating for black rights, you
have Booker T. Washington, whom we
talked about earlier, and a new one for
you web Duke boys who simply demanded
full civil rights. Finally, the last two
progressive movements were immigration
and the environment. Immigration exposed
a split down the middle. Some
progressives pushed restrictions, while
others focused on supporting immigrants
and cities. Environmental reform
followed a similar pattern, dividing
into preservationists, who wanted to
protect nature for its own sake, and
conservationists who emphasized
responsible long-term resource
management. Despite their differences,
both supported the creation of national
parks. Welcome to the A push version of
World War I. If you wonder why I have to
preface that by saying a push version,
it's because this war is technically
mostly an aspect of European history. I
mean, the war started in Europe. It
mostly happened in Europe and it ended
in Europe. So, from a US history
perspective, I would personally love to
go in and explain every tiny little
battle and complexity of this war. But I
can't. All I'm going to do here is give
you a little bit of context and explain
the US side of things. So, basically, by
1914, all these European powers had a
bunch of weapons. They were all
entangled in a bunch of alliances. And
most of all, they were all pretty full
of themselves. After some dude got
assassinated, one country declared war
on another country, which would cause a
big domino reaction because of the
alliances we talked about earlier. Which
is why my favorite historical newspaper
has got to be this amazing one from The
Onion. So anyway, this war happens for a
while and by 1916, the war stalemates
into two big battles of trench warfare
at Verdun and the S. But if you're
wondering what the US is doing,
basically nothing is the answer. The US
wanted to maintain neutrality during
this war. However, it still sent ships
full of supplies to its allies. But then
you see two big things happen. First is
Germany's unrestricted submarine warfare
kept sinking ships with Americans on
them. The most famous of this was the
sinking of the Lucatania. Then by 1917,
after the sinking started up again,
America got one more push to enter the
war, the Zimmerman telegram. This was an
encrypted message to Mexico from Germany
intercepted by Britain. It basically
tried to get Mexico to declare war on
the US if the US entered the war. So
this plus the constant sinking of
civilian ships caused America to enter
the war in April of 1917. Now I want you
to understand the American soldiers sent
to Europe known as the American
Expeditionary Forces played a relatively
limited role in combat. That being said,
this combined with constant American
supplies allowed the war to tip in favor
of the allies and eventually Germany
would lose. This war would end with the
Treaty of Versailles and this will
easily be probably one of the most
biggest controversies in world history.
This treaty will basically force all
blame of the war on Germany and cause
them to pay an insane amount of
reparations. The US president at the
time, Woodro Wilson, also wanted to
create a League of Nations to try an
ally to make sure a war like this can
never happen again. However, Wilson will
fail to bring a Republican to the
discussion, which will cause him to lose
Republican support in Congress. And
ironically, despite him coming up with
the idea, Congress will choose for the
US not to join the League of Nations.
And just for numbers sakes here, about
20 million people died in World War I.
And for reference, only about a 100,000
will be from the US. The last video we
talked about World War I in Europe.
However, this is US history, so why
don't we now go back to America and take
a look at what it's like during and
after the war. Here's a good rule to go
by. For both World Wars and American
history, America is going to become kind
of unstable. I mean, we already know
lots of America is racist. I mean, Jim
Crow laws still exist and are still
being enforced quite a lot. But now,
there are genuine threats in Europe that
America declares as enemies when they
enter the war. And so, during and after
the war, many Americans will become more
willing to limit civil liberties,
especially freedom of speech because of
anxiety about disloyalty, radical
political ideas, and labor unrest. Good
examples here are the Espionage and
Sedation Acts, which were acts that
criminalized anti-war speech and the use
of quote disloyal language. You also
have the American Protective League or
the APL, who literally volunteered to
report [music] suspicious people. And
after the Russian Revolution started in
1917, a period in American history known
as the first Red Scare happened where
there was a big fear that communists,
anarchists, and other radicals were
threatening the United States. Now,
let's transition and talk about
immigration. Because before World War I,
immigration from Europe reached very
high levels. After the war, nivism,
which was the belief that the interests
of nativeborn Americans should be
protected against immigrants, increased.
This is where you now see quotas being
implemented, like the emergency quota
act and the 1924 immigration act, which
would both place numerical limits on
immigration by creating quotas based on
national origin. A quick note that
because of increased wartime production,
there was a big movement of people from
small towns into big industrial cities
for factory work. Now, this factory work
will mostly be in the north, and a whole
bunch of African-Americans still live
down south where they are being forced
to adhere to Jim Crow laws and have
basically no economic opportunities. So,
now when word gets out that the North
has lots of high-paying factory jobs
available, something known as the great
migration happens, where a bunch of
African-Americans will move out of the
south to the north. Now, this would
create new black communities. But I do
want to teach something that actually is
rarely taught in American history. That
is something known as the red summer of
1919. This is an effect of the great
migration where there will be a lot of
white mobs attacking black communities
in dozens of US cities and towns. Oh,
the roaring 20s. What a time to be
alive. Oops, sorry, but that's actually
supposed to be next topic. Lots of
people like studying the 1920s in
American history because of how much
cool culture there was, which is why we
refer to it as the roaring 20s. Right
now, we're going to talk about what
facilitated and caused this quote
roaring 20s. Basically, this comes down
to two things. New technology and mass
media. Let's first talk about the
technology and for this we will look at
two people. Let's start with Henry Ford.
Ford here popularized something very
revolutionary known as assembly lines.
Meaning he broke down production into
simple repeated steps causing a faster
output which would then cause the price
of goods to go down. The second part to
this is something called scientific
management where you prioritize
efficiency over everything else. The man
attributed to this is a man named
Frederick Taylor. Oh, and before we move
on, the biggest innovation in this time
period, and arguably in the entirety of
world history, will be the automobile.
It's truly indescribable how much the
automobile changes everything. Commuting
changes, roads will be built, gas
stations, and motel are made, and it
would cause an unforeseen level of
suburban growth. But now, let's go over
to our second thing and talk about the
media. Because other than the
automobile, you have two more things
that boomed in this [music] time period.
Cinema in the radio. With cinema, we are
obviously talking about the growth of
Hollywood and movies, which would give
Americans shared celebrities, fashion,
slang, and even values. The more
impactful one here though is probably
radios because now instead of waiting
for a newspaper, people can have live
broadcasts, news, music, sports,
advertising. And the big importance here
is that people across the country are
all listening to the same stuff. This
created a consumer economy, meaning
people are buying appliances, cars, and
entertainment, often through credit and
installment plans. This would also
facilitate the means of which cultures
will spread across America throughout
the 20s, especially regional ones, and
make something like the Roaring 20s
possible. Oh, the Roaring 20s. What a
time to be alive. So much culture to
find this era of American history. So,
why don't we walk down this 1920s street
and explore some cultural phenomena? The
first stop on this street is the lovely
bar, which we call a speak easy, because
obviously alcohol is illegal in this
time period after the 18th amendment.
Look at those lovely flappers dancing on
stage. While behind them, a jazz band
fills the room with fast-paced rhythms
that symbolize a break from tradition
and the rise of a new American sound.
The bar is packed with people from
different backgrounds, a rare sight for
the time, all gathered in defiance of
one thing, prohibition. But the bar
isn't the only thing we see. Our next
stop is Harland, New York, where the
great migration has caused a surge of
African-American culture known as the
Harlem Renaissance. In the building down
the street, I think I see two people,
Zoranil Hursten and Langston Hughes, who
are proving that black people can write
great literature. But coming up closer,
I see two great artists of Bessie Smith
and Lily Armstrong creating and
performing lovely jazz to all that can
behold it. Our last stop here is the
local library where women finally gain
new visibility in society with their new
right to vote in women's suffrage
movement. And I think I even catch a
sight of Alice Paul in the corner
helping out. Man, this era of American
history is truly something special. All
right, that's enough of that. Yes, this
era looks incredible on the surface.
However, it's kind of hard to explain,
but it's all kind of empty and trashy
below the surface. Prohibition causes
widespread crime and the growth of civil
unrest on top of numerical quotas.
Immigrants get treated even worse with
these two Supreme Court decisions. And
though this era is defined by vast
amounts of money everywhere, you got to
remember what comes literally right
after this era. The 1920s is all surface
level. And the reason it will collapse
so quickly when the depression hits is
because everything is built on beliefs
and borrowed money. The whole era seems
cute and incredible on the surface, but
truly everything you see is hanging on a
tight thread. So before we end this
topic, I think it's only right since we
talked about all the good. Let's talk
about the famous bad things that
happened in the 20s. The Scopes monkey
trial upheld a Tennessee law banning the
teaching of evolution. In Buck versus
Bell, the Supreme Court ruled that it
was okay to remove some people's ability
to have children known as sterilization.
And finally, Nicolasako and Bartal
Benzetti had a very unfair murder trial,
likely because of their Italian
heritage, and they got sentenced to
death and executed despite their likely
innocence. On the surface, the 1920s was
great. It truly was. I mean, do you
remember back to units one and two of
this course where we talked about
America being founded on people living
in the rural countryside? Now, we have
gone so far with so many big
corporations that in the 20s it will be
the first time in American history where
there's more people living in big urban
cities than in the rural countryside.
So, if the 20s are so glamorous, how
exactly can something like the Great
Depression even happen? Here's your
answer with four reasons. The first is
simply overprouction because the
American economy was so industrial that
during the 20s it produced more goods
than people could buy. The second is
debt because pretty much all consumers
and businesses were deeply in debt. The
reason for that is that all the lavish
things bought by these people in the 20s
were purchased through things like
credit and not actual real paper money.
The third one here though is a
bank/federal reserve failure because
banks were giving out risky loans, had
little oversight and collapsed when
people rushed to withdraw their money
and the Federal Reserve didn't step in
to help. And finally, the fourth reason
was the economy around the world was not
that great. European economies depended
on US loans after World War I. So when
[music] US banks collapsed, loans were
recalled. And with all these four causes
in play, it's like a room full of gas
that requires one spark for the whole
room to go boom. And that spark will be
when the stock market crashes in 1929.
Pretty quickly, the Great Depression
will be devastating. Millions will lose
their jobs, homes, and savings. The
unemployment rate will shoot up to a
staggering 25%. Millions who couldn't
afford food lined up in historically
long bread lines where there was never
enough food to go around. And people who
lost their homes built makeshift
shelters out of scrap wood and
cardboard, which would make shanty towns
known as quote Hoovervilles. Families
would migrate all over the place to
search for work. and children would
often go without school. As for the
initial federal response, it will be
quite weak and be based on voluntary
cooperation between businesses and
government. Pretty quickly, when this
doesn't work, America will redefine
itself in the ideas of modern American
liberalism. This will call for the
regulation of markets, social insurance,
and most importantly, responsibility in
the hands of government for economic
well-being. That means bye-bye lass far.
It was nice knowing you. So there's this
big misconception through the
understanding of US history that the
Great Depression happens and right
afterwards the New Deal comes along and
ends the Great Depression. To put it
bluntly, no, the New Deal does not end
the Great Depression. The technical end
comes with the mobilization for World
War II. I'd say the New Deal itself is
more of something that reshaped the US
government. So let's recap here. Herbert
Hoover is president, the depression
starts, and poor old lad Hoover over
here doesn't really know what to do and
is criticized heavily for it. So when
Franklin Delanor Roosevelt or FDR came
along as the Democratic nominee in the
1932 election, it's a pretty simple and
easy victory for him fairly quickly. FDR
will implement his New Deal plan. And
this is quite complex, but to give it a
sentence definition, FDR's New Deal will
use aggressive government intervention
to stabilize the economy, put people
back to work, and prevent another
depression from happening again. The
method that will be used here is
something we like to call the three Rs:
relief, recovery, and reform. Very
quickly, you'll start seeing programs.
Let's go through a few of them. The
Civilian Conservation Corps employed
young men in environmental and
infrastructure projects. There were lots
of public work/infrastructure programs
that built roads, parks, dams, schools,
and public buildings, and separate
programs existed for Native Americans,
Puerto Rico, and African-Americans. If
you can't tell, all of these existed so
there would be more jobs for people to
get. But what I want you to notice here
is the big contradiction of what we
established back in unit 6. Do you
remember when America functioned on a
hands-off approach and letting the
economy do its own thing? Now with this
New Deal, it will easily be up to this
point in history the biggest government
intervention in its own economy that
America has ever had. And since this New
Deal changed American policy so much,
there was quite a lot of debates on both
sides of Roosevelt. Radicals, unions,
and populist movements such as Hugh Long
and Father Charles Coughlin will push
Roosevelt to intervene as much as
possible with government efforts. But on
the other side, conservatives in
Congress and the Supreme Court sought to
limit the New Deal's overall scope. An
example of this is the Supreme Court
case Shrek Poultry Corp versus the
United States, which struck down parts
of the National Industry Recovery Act.
And finally, the last thing about the
New Deal is the institutions it created
that still exists to this day. The
GlassSteagall Act separated commercial
banking from investment banking, and the
Social Security Act gave old age
pensions, unemployment insurance, and
aid for the disabled. If you can't tell,
everything about this New Deal will
cause workingclass communities to
identify more with the Democratic Party.
So, we are currently positioned squarely
in the inter war period in American
history. So, here's a good question to
ask after World War I. Should America
lead globally or stay out of foreign
conflicts? If you want to know the
answer to this question, it is mostly to
stay out of everything, meaning to be
isolationist. However, there were quite
a few things that happened that went
against this ideology. The first of this
is two things. The DAW plan was made
because Germany could not pay for its
reparations and Europe was struggling as
a result. So the plan was to loan
Germany money which after Germany paid
their reparations allowed Britain and
France to pay off their US war debts.
Then later the Kellogg brand pact was
passed in which most countries pledged
to not solve world problems with war.
And if you can't tell both of these
things did not work. The DAW plan failed
because of the Great Depression and the
Kellogg Brand Pact failed because there
was no way it could be enforced. It's
also important to note that the US
continued intervention and continued
presence in Latin America and the
Caribbean such as in Haiti and
Nicaragua. But now we see something else
rise in Europe and that is a very famous
mustache man with an ideology of fascism
growing very strong. The US sensed war
might come and pass a series of
neutrality acts which didn't really
work. And over in Europe, our good
friend Hitler is conquering land and the
horrible method of appeasement isn't
alleviating it. Once FDR realizes these
Axis powers are dangerous, he slowly
starts moving away from isolationism.
And then out of nowhere, bam, the naval
base Pearl Harbor is bombed by the Axis
power Japan and America officially
enters World War II. So the US is now
officially in World War II. But to put
it bluntly, US entry into World War II
required total economic mobilization.
That means all the work needed to make
cars, tanks, and weapons will cause so
much jobs, which effectively will end
the Great Depression. And here's another
part to this. All the men are getting
shipped off to war. That means the
people that will step up to do this
factory work will mostly be women. That
means during the war, women had many new
gains as they took over male-dominated
jobs. However, it should be noted many
women were pushed out of the jobs after
the war when men returned. But women
aren't the only one that get
opportunities. African-Americans do as
well. They will also work in factories.
However, they will face their own share
of racism. But the other people that get
opportunities here are immigrants and
migrants. There will be so much
migration to big cities that places like
Los Angeles, Oakland, Seattle, and
Detroit will grow like crazy. The
specific immigrants I want to mention
here are Mexican ones because you start
seeing a vast amount of Mexican
immigrants that entered the US during
the war under the Breretta program which
allowed Mexican laborers to temporarily
work in US agriculture and railroad
jobs. I'm sure you can guess, but the
response you'll see to this is racism.
An example of that is the Zoot Sweet
riots where Mexicans and Filipinos were
attacked in LA over a series of days.
And the last thing I want to say is a
lot of people like to say FDR was one of
the greatest presidents. I won't really
say anything on the matter, but here is
something that doesn't look too good on
his part. During World War II, fear and
racism led FDR to issue an executive
order which would force around 120,000
Japanese Americans into internment
camps. And these camps were not good in
the slightest. It's time to talk about
World War II. This war will be like no
other in history. The US will directly
fight Japan in the Pacific theater, and
the Allied powers will fight Germany in
Europe. After Pearl Harbor in Congress's
Declaration of War, Americans will view
this war as a fight for the survival of
freedom and democracy against fascist
and militaristic ideologies. And this
view on the war isn't too far off from
the truth because later in the war, it
was realized the horrible things the
Axis powers were up to. In Germany,
minorities with a special emphasis on
Jewish citizens will be forced into
horrible concentration death camps where
it is said that over 6 million Jewish
will die. Over in Japan, their invasion
of China will showcase horrific
tragedies such as the rape of Nank King,
where Chinese civilians and disarmed
soldiers were mass murdered, raped, and
looted. Fascism posed such a threat that
this war was about more than just
victory or defeat. Like in World War I,
the Allies had to win or the world would
be fundamentally changed. America
quickly recognized this, leading to full
national mobilization. industry surged
and women and minorities joined the war
effort through groups like the women's
army auxiliary corpse and anai units of
Japanese American soldiers. So let's go
over to the war now. We'll first talk
about the European theater. Basically by
1944, Germany had conquered France and
part of the Soviet Union. On the eastern
side, the winter allowed the Soviets to
regroup and push back against Germany
with probably the most important turning
point battle in world history being the
battle of Stalenrad. On the western
side, the Allies needed to push back
against Germany. So on June 6th, 1944, a
combination of American, British, and
Canadian forces stormed the northern
beaches of France, which was known as
D-Day. This was a huge success, and the
Allied forces will continue pushing on
the west, while the Soviets will push on
the east, and eventually Hitler will be
defeated. Now, let's head over to the
Pacific theater. The turning point
battle here is when America will destroy
a bunch of Japanese aircraft carriers,
and that will happen at the Battle of
Midway. After Midway, America will start
taking back islands that Japan had
conquered during the war. However, this
will reveal a grim reality. Japanese
soldiers fought with extreme brutality,
and their code of honor compelled them
to fight to the death, making the island
hopping campaign extremely brutal and
costly. By the end of the war, America
had developed the atomic bomb thanks to
the Manhattan Project. This bomb would
kill so many people, but it could force
the fierce Japanese to surrender. And
with so many American soldiers dying in
this island hopping, America would be
forced to make a difficult choice. And I
think Oppenheimer will put it best. Now
I am become death, the destroyer of
worlds.
>> Two Abombs will be dropped. Hundreds of
thousands of innocent people will die.
Japan will surrender and it will be one
of the biggest moral debates for the
rest of history. World War II was just
simply devastating. Around 80 million
people will die over the course of this
six-year long war. However, the thing
about this war from a US history
perspective is that this war was pretty
much fought everywhere except the US.
After the war, Europe and Asia will be
devastated in both casualties and land.
I mean, just look at these images on the
screen. So now the US will have a
massive military, industrial capacity
and mostly untouched land meaning
finally the United States will emerge as
the most powerful country in the world
upon the conclusion of this war. The
Yaltta and Potam conferences will happen
near the end of the war. The key
outcomes you should know are that
Germany will be divided into occupation
zones. Japan will be occupied and
rebuilt under US supervision. War crime
trials will be held against Nazi leaders
and borders/governments across Europe
and Asia will be reorganized. But the
other consequence of this war is the
creation of the United Nations or UN.
This will allow countries to negotiate,
prevent wars, and promote cooperation.
But very quickly, you'll see the Soviet
Union occupy most of Eastern Europe,
enforce a communist ideology, which will
lead to a different kind of war that we
refer to as being very cold. But I think
we'll cover that next unit. My goodness,
I think this is the longest unit review
I've ever done. Thank you all for
watching and please consider watching
this video and subscribing to my noted
educational channel. In fact, before we
end this video, I have a good question
for you. What's your guys's opinion on
the atomic bomb debate? If you made it
this far, please feel free to let me
know in the comments. Anyway, I'll see
you all. Bye-bye.